DAN MORRISS

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

L +44 7919 288949

- ✓ danielmorrissl@gmail.com
- 🚯 <u>danmorriss.dev</u> Wiltshire, UK
- in linkedin.com/in/morrissdaniel

EXECUTIVE SUMMARY

Junior Software Developer with a Diploma in Full Stack Software Development from the Code Institute. Proficient in HTML, CSS, Javascript & Python. I have 15 years experience using technology in the Music Industry. I am a valuable teamplayer with strong communication skills and effective problem solving abilities. I am eager to gain entry into an exciting development team where I can grow and contribute.

EDUCATION

Code Institute & the University of West Scotland

March 2023 - 2024 Full Stack Software Development Diploma

University of West London

Sept 2017 - 2019 Licentiate Degree in Music Tuition

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Developer

January 2022 - Present

- Designed & built custom websites for clients across various industries, showcasing versatility in design and functionality.
- Managed projects efficiently, ensuring clear communication and timely delivery.
- Optimized website performance through innovative technologies and best practices.

Director & Music Tutor

Morriss Music Ltd. March 2019 - Present

- Built a website & blog for selling sheet music & courses that grew my credibility.
- Architected smooth booking & invoicing systems, allowing students to manage lessons & payments easily.
- Created an online ukulele course with interactive practice capabilities allowing my student base to grow.

Electric Guitar Tutor & Studio Manager

Cheam School / October 2019 - April 2022

- Arranged and recorded live performances resulting in music scholarships for students.
- Mentored school pop and jazz bands for performances and tours.
- Wrote individual learning paths for students to achieve high exam grades resulting in extra UCAS points.

SKILLS

- → HTML
- → CSS
- → JavaScript
- → Python
- → PostgreSQL
- → React
- → Django
- → Django Rest Framework
- → Bootstrap
- → Git

COURSES

JS30

Wes Boz JavaScript (30 Hours)

Concering Responsive Layouts

Kevin Powell CSS (30 Hours)

Complete React Developer

Redux, Hooks, GraphQL, Stripe, Firebase (42 hours)

PORTFOLIO

Highlights

Social media app built using React & Django REST Framework

Niall's Barber Shop

Booking system for a local barbershop built with Django & PostgreSQL

Retro Mashup Mayhem

Hackathon project: Retro JavaScript platform game built with Kaboom.js